Windmuller, John P. Additional Papers /4158
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
John P. Windmuller Additional Papers
1955-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Windmuller, John P.
/4158
18 cubic feet
18 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
3108803
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 03, 2016
Biographical / Historical
John P. Windmuller (December 4, 1923 - December 2, 2003) was Professor of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University's New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
A graduate of the University of Illinois (BA, 1948) and Cornell University's ILR School (PhD, 1951), Windmuller joined the Cornell University faculty in 1951. He was appointed the Martin P. Catherwood Professor of Industrial and Labor Relations in 1983. He was named professor emeritus in 1987.
An expert in the study of international and comparative labor relations, Windmuller authored many books and reports on the topic, among them Collective Bargaining in Industrial Market Economies: A Reappraisal (ILO, 1987) and Labor Relations in the Netherlands (Ithaca: Cornell, 1969). With Alan Gladstone, he edited Employer Associations and Industrial Relations: A Comparative Study (New York: Oxford, 1984).
See the Cornell University Faculty Memorial Statement for Professor John Windmuller: http://hdl.handle.net/1813/18116
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3028: John P. Windmuller Records /4046: ILR School Historical School Documents /4065: John P. Windmuller Additional Papers /4146: John Windmuller Additional Papers
Windmuller, John P.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3108803
- Concluding Lecture Convergence + Diversity in Industrial Relations, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Concluding Lecture - Convergence + Diversity in Industrial Relations (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Concluding Lecture - Convergence + Diversity in Industrial Relations (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Windmuller - Lecture Notes (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Windmuller ILR Lecture Cassette 9/24/93, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bean Comparative Industrial Relations, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- ILR 330 Permission to Reproduce Articles, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 330/530 Fall 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 330/530 - Windmuller Fall 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 330/530 - Attendance Sheets, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ILR 330/530 - Fall 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 330/530 - Fall 1988 John P. Windmuller (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ILE 330 Course Outline, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ILR 330 Course Questionnaires, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- JPW- Course Evaluation Form, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- ILR 330 Sample Exams, 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- OECD Statistics, 1979-1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Union Membership as an Approximate Percent, 1950-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Union Membership Trends in Great Britain (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Stoppages in Progress, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- British Election Results, 1945-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Ford Motor Company Agreement (U.K.), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- British Engineering, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Davies- The Law and Forms of Trade Union Representation in the 1980s: The British Case, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- The Economist- "Business in Britain", 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Fulcher- "On the Expli. Relations Diversity: in Britain and Sweden, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Nolan P. "Walking on Water? Performan and Industrial Relations, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Poole- IR: Origins and Patterns of National Diversity, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Towers "British Trade Unions: Context, Crisis and Response, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Historical Background Great Britain (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Nissan Motor Manufact. And Amalgamated Union of Engineering Workers, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Roberts, "Recent Trends in CB in GB", 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Rico, "The New IR: British Electricians' New Style Agreements", 1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Wedderburn, "The New Industrial Relations Laws in GB", 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Union Membership Trends in Sweden (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Historical Background Sweden (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Swedish Basic Agreement, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Swedish Engineering Collective Agreement, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Albage, "Recent Trends in CB in Sweden", 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Organization of SAF, LO, TCO and SACO/SR (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Composition - Swedish Parliam., 1976-1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Gourevitich-"Unions and Economic Crisis in Sweden", 1951 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Lash "The End of Necorporatism?: The Breakdown of Centralized Barg. In (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Mydral, "Collective Wage Earner Funds in Sweden", 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Neal- "Change and The Trade Union Movement in Sweden", 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Peterson "Swedish CB-A Changing Scene" (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Swedish Info. Service, Working Life in Sweden, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Renault Agreement, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Excerpts from Renault Agreement -T.U. Rights, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Historical Background France (Box 2, Folder 20)
- France Labor-Mgt. Interface (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Results of Elections to French Works Councils, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- France - Union Membership (Box 2, Folder 23)
- France-Nomenklatura (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Aldir, L, "The American Model Unrealized: A Reevaluation of Plant", 1974-1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Bridgford, Jeff, "French Trade Unions: Crisis in the 1980's,", 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Caire, "Recent Trends in CB in France", 1984 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Delamotte, "Recent C.B. Trends in France", 1985 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Union Membership in West Germany (Box 2, Folder 29)
- VW Contract, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- VW-Metalworkers Agreement, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Codetermination in West Germany, 1952-1972 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Unionization in Twelve German Industries, 1961-1975 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Adams, "Workers Participation in Management in West Germany", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Berghahn and Karsten "Industrial Relations in West Germany," (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Furstenburg, "Recent Trends in CB in the Federal Rep. of Germany, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Schergle, "The German Model", 1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Streeck-Co-determination: The Fourth Decade, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Streeck- "Industrial Relations in West Germany, 1980-1987" (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Conflict at Ford-Genk (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Union Membership in the Netherlands, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Albeda, "Recent Trends in C.B. in the Neth.", 1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Clarke, Labour-Mgt. Disputes: A Perspective, 1955-1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- EIRR-Netherlands: Board-Level Participation (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Flanagan-Unionism, Economic Stabilization, and Income Policies: The Netherlands, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Working Days Lost in Industrial Disputes, 1978-1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Selected Data on Strikes (330/530), 1972-1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- 19-Year Averages (1977-1986) (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Union Membership as an Approximate Percentage, 1955-1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Cella and Treu, "National Trade Union Movements" (Box 3, Folder 12)
- W.E. Political Parties (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Brooks-Theory and Practice in Soviet Labour Law, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Tavitian-Trade Union Trends in Western Europe: A European Perspective (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Yanaev, G.I. "Perestroika and Trade Unions in USSR,", 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Gorbachev, "The Role of the Trade Unions,", 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- 334/534 - Spring, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Spring 1989 -- Mini-Course ILR 334/534 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- ITF News, "A New Dawn for Trade Unions in East and Central Europe", 1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- ITF News, "A New Dawn for Trade Unions in East and Central Europe", 1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- International Confederation of Trade Unions (334/534), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- ILR 331 Course Outline, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- ILR 331 Guidelines for Term Papers, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- ILR 331/531 Midterm Exam Sample, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- ILR 331 Evaluations, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Blum, Nigeria, 1940-1965 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Damacho. "Industrial Relations in Africa", 1975 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- de Schweinitz (July 1959) (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Kemble in Free Trade Union News (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Lowit in Journal of Industrial Relations, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Martens, "Trade Union and the Political Process in Africa" (Box 3, Folder 32)
- "Martens, "Unity Eludes Africa's Trade Unions", 1985 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- MEHTA, Economic Development and Cultural Change, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- MEHTA, "The Mediating Role of the Trade Union", 1958 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- MESA-LAGO, "Club in the 1970's (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Miller, in JIR, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Patrick and Rosovsky Asia's New Giant, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Grancelli, Soviet Management and Labor Relations, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Ruble, "Soviet Trade Unions", 1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Shalayer, The Soviet Trade Unions and Restructuring (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Fisher: The Economic Role of Unions in Less Developed Areas (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Excerpts from Const. and Bylaws of USSR T.T.'s, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Ford and it's Workers, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Collective Agreement of the Workers' Red Banner, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Ramaswamy and Ramaswamy, "Industry and Labor", 1965 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Gdansk Agreement, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Statutes of Indep. Solidarity Labor Unions (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Keenoy, "Solidarity: The Anti-Trade Union", 1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Yugoslav Enterprises, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Yugo. Mgt. Structure of Orgs. Of Associated Labor (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Doder, The Yugoslavs Chapter 6 and 7, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Sinha and Sinha, Structure and Gov't of Indian T.U.'s (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Indian T.U. Structure (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Indian Strike Statistics, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Kassalow in Journal of Industrial Relations, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Japanese Diet, 1969-1989 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Union Membership and Density Rates in Japan (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Shirai, "Recent Trends in Collective Barg. In Japan", 1984 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- An Airline Under Siege El and It's Employee, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Histadrut (Box 4, Folder 26)
- ILR 430 Fall 1992 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- ILR 430 - Windmuller, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- 430 - Fall 1990- Windmuller (Box 4, Folder 29)
- American Historical Review Snell, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- American Historical Review Snell, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- American Historical Review Snell, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Landauer - European Socialism (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Landauer - European Socialism (Box 4, Folder 34)
- 'Skrzypczak', 1971 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- 'Skrzypczak', 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Slomp Labor Relations in Europe, 1971-1981 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Slomp - Labor Relations in Europe (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Slomp - Labor Relations in Europe (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Schoenbaum - Hitler's Social Revolution (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Schoenbaum - Hitler's Social Revolution (Box 4, Folder 41)
- ILR 430 Course Outline, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- ILR 430 Sidelines for Term Papers, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- ILR 430 Evaluations, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- ILR 430 Sample Exam Midterm, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- ILR 430 Sample Exam (Final), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Basic Reference Sources, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- 430- Political Party Representation in the Reichstag (2 Stage), 1919-1933 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Extension of Trade Unionism, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Union M'Ship Data, 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- John Hattersley Testimony, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- LeChapelier Law, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Party Representation in the Reichstag, 1972-1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- ILR 630 Course Outline, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- ILR 630 Evaluations, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- ILR 630 Final Exam Sample (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Asian Seminar on Multinationals (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Comptroller General, "Sustaining Improved U.S. Participation, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Extract from Guidelines for Multinational Enterprise (OECD), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- MNC Tables, 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Godson, The AFL Foreigh Policy Making, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- ILO Declaration of Principles (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Kemble, Eugenia, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Logue, Toward a Theory of T.U. Internationalism (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Reports of the AFL-CIO Executive Council 1985 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Schultz "U.S. Role in the ILO", 1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Social Conditions Attached to Sweden Investment G. Scheme (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Thalmayer Case (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Weisz, "U.S. Labor and International Affairs" (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Windmuller 330//50 Panl. Cop. Lecture 9/10/91, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Cassette
- Windmuller 330/530 Lecture - Oct. 15, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- ILR 330 Windmuller Sept. 18 '91, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Mediamate Floppy Disc Case - Lectures (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Mediamate Floppy Disc Case - Backups for JP Windmuller, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- African American Labor Center, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Asian-American Free Labor Institute (AAFLI), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- African Correspondence, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Alumni, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- The Annals, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Arbitration, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- ASIA - Other Countries, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Australian Correspondence, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- B - General Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Belgium Correspondence, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- British Correspondence, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- British Correspondence I-Z, 1979-1992 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Canadian Correspondence, 1977-1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Career Services - ILR, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Robert Copp, 1980-1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Cornachio, Kevin, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Dean Doherty, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- DGB, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- The Economist Magazine, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Economia E Lavoro (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Encyclopedia, 1978-1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Europe - Other Countries, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Foreign Visitors 1965 - (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Foundations General, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- French Correspondence, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Friedrich-Ebert-Stiftung Foundation, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- German Correspondence 1965 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- German Marshall Fund, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Hilton International, 1965-1973 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- ICFTU - General 1970- (Box 7, Folder 18)
- ILO A-G, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- ILO H-Z, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- ILR Faculty, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- ILO Institute Correspondence, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- ILR -- Internal, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Indian Correspondence, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Metalworkers (IMF), 1933 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- International Trade Secretariatt -- Its, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Israel Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Japan Correspondence, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Kassalow, Everett M., 1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Labor Attaches Foreign, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Labor Attaches United States, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Latin American Correspondence, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Lipsky, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- McKersie, Robert, 1975-1983 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Netherlands A-B, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Netherlands I-Z, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- OECD, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Northup and Rowan, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Office of Student Services, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Oxford University Press, 1982-1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Publishers, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Dean Rehmus, 1981-1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Scandinavian Correspondence, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Sturmthal, Adolf, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Swedish Info Service, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Turkish Correspondence, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- U.S. Department of Labor 1962- (Box 9, Folder 11)
- U.S. Department of State 1964- (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Western Societies Prgm., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- World Confederation of Labor, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Corresp. A-D, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Corresp. E-G, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous Corresp. H-R, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Corresp. S-Z, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous 1982 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- A, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- B, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- C-E, 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- F-G, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- H-J, 1976-1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- K-L, 1967-1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- M-O, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- P-Q-R, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- S, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- T-Z, 1974-1978 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Recommendations A-D, 1969-1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Recommendations E-J, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Recommendations N-S, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Recommendations T-Z, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Alumni -- Saratoga, 1988-1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Annual Reports To Dean (JPW), 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Book Reviews, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Book Reviews - Netherlands, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Brooks Report, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- CIS -- Exec. Com. Materials, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- CIS -- Western Societies Program, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- CISER, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Collective Bargaining, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Commission on Common Learning, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Cornell University Press, 1982-1986 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- CU Press Board of Editors, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- CU Press Review Committee, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Dean's Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Extension Program, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- FCR Executive Com., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Faculty Legislation, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Faculty Materials, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Faculty Materials 1962- (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Faculty Minutes Summary Index, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Faculty Minutes 1981- (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Faculty Minutes 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Faculty Minutes 1966-1970 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Faculty Minutes 1966-1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Faculty Minutes 1961-1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Faculty Minutes 1956-1960 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Faculty Minutes 1951-1955 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Graduate Program, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Grade Books (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Graduate Program in New York City, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Internal Review Committee, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- International and Comparative Labor Relations - 1953 - (Box 13, Folder 8)
- ICLR Department Minutes 1963- (Box 13, Folder 9)
- ICLR Department of Courses, Etc. 1963- (Box 13, Folder 10)
- ILR Press, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- ILR Report, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- ILR, 1977-1993 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- ILR Review, 1970-1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Library, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Nominations, Elections, and Personnel Policies Committee, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Personnel Policies Committee 1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Non-Voting Worship - Voting Rights, 1972-1988 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Grievances, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Personnel Policies, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- University Faculty Materials --1966- (Box 14, Folder 8)
- University Faculty Minutes --1966- (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Thomson, Andrew W.J., 1961-1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Baderschneider, Jean, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Heath, Mollie, 1970-1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Cogill, Charles, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Efren, Cordova, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Dayal, Sahab, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Gathercole, Michael, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Ghosh, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Grazier, Martin, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Johannesen, Jannette, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- King, Donovan, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Kumalo, Mhambi, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Markham, James, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- McDermott, Pat, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Mellor, Julie, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Plakias, Dean, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Reddy, Julie, 1981-1985 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Rey-Salvador, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Schalekamp, Robert J., 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Peter Scherer, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Selden, Martha M., 1973-1977 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Schmidt, Hans, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Robin Siegal, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- David Siemens, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Troyer, Steve, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Walsh, Louise, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Zupan, Nada, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Lipperman, Peter, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Case, Cynthia, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Arbitration American LaFrance, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Arbitration Armstrong Cork, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Arbitration Crowley, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Arbitration GAF Corporation, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Arbitration Gould's Pumps, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Arbitration - Hooker, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Arbitration Hussman Self-Contained (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Arbitration Plattsburgh AFB, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Arbitration Sterling Drug, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Administrative Correspondence, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Course Load, 1975-1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- NYSSILR, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- 1988-89 Search Committee International Comparative Labor Relations Professor, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Dean's Search 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Dean's Search '87, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Dean Search 1987 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Search Committee Candidate, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Search Comm. in '85, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Search Committee, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Department Chairmen, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Grades, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Graduate Committee Admissions, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- ILR Faculty/Alumni Retreat, 1977-1988 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- MILR Review Committee, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Outside Review Panel, 1977-1987 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Search Committee -- University Librarian, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Search Committees Resumes - Active, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Search Committee Resumes - Inactive, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Schurman Chairs, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Undergraduate Program, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- University Librarian Review Com., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Williams, Alan, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Windmuller - S Correspondence, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Travel - John Windmuller, 1990-1994 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- European Handbook, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- List of International Files (Box 18, Folder 4)
- JW - Library Work Orders, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Bibliography Instructions JPW Windmuller's, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- J. Windmuller (Personal), 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- J. Windmuller (Resumes), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Statements, 1988-1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Books Reviewed, 1968-1989 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Books Ordered, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Monograph - U.S.D.L. Windmuller, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 13)